Guide to the Andrea Parrot papers, 1970-2009
Parrot, Andrea papers, 1970-2009
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Andrea Parrot papers, 1970-2009
23-26-3836
Andrea. Parrot
1.1 cubic foot
Correspondence, Manuscripts, Photographs, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files reflecting Prof. Parrot's involvement in the Center for Crime Victim and Sexual Assault Services of Tompkins County, originally Ithaca Rape Crisis, and subject files about violence against women, including newspaper clippings, some letters and press releases, and a few photographs, from the 1970s through 2009.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of Policy Analysis and Management, College of Human Ecology, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files reflecting Prof. Parrot's involvement in the Center for Crime Victim and Sexual Assault Services of Tompkins County, originally Ithaca Rape Crisis, and subject files about violence against women, including newspaper clippings, some letters and press releases, and a few photographs, from the 1970s through 2009.
Includes Parrot's publications.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Parrot, Andrea.; Center for Crime Victim and Sexual Assault Services of Tompkins County--Ithaca, N.Y.
Subjects:
Women--Violence against.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (date unknown) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis Media Releases (2000-2009) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History: National Crime Victims' Rights Week (2003) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (2003) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (2002) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (2001) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (2000) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1999) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1998) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1997) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1996) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1995) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1994) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1992) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1991) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1990) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1989) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1988) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1987) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1985) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1984) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History: People vs. Liberta (1984) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1983) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1982) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1981) (Box 1)
- CVSA/Ithaca Rape Crisis History (1980) (Box 1)
- CVSA (Center for Crime Victim and Sexual Assault Services of Tompkins County - Formerly Ithaca Rape Crisis) History: Part 1 (1970s) (Box 1)
- CVSA (Center for Crime Victim and Sexual Assault Services of Tompkins County - Formerly Ithaca Rape Crisis) History: Part 2 (1970s) (Box 1)
- Parrot's Publications 1980s-1990s (Box 2)